Howard!
Ray... You have...
to live.
Is that... overheating?
Vrăjitorul cu săbii de gheață va conduce lumea
Episodul 1
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest
Sorcerer Enters the Academy of Sorcery
It really is huge.
Let's see...
Which way is the auditorium?
Îmi cer scuze,
domniță.
Oh, vai. Este în regulă.
But I'm not sure it's a good idea to
suddenly stop in the middle of the path.
Îmi cer scuze. E prima oară când vin aici.
What? But didn't all new students
move onto campus two days ago?
I heard there'd be just one moving in
on the day of the entrance ceremony!
One who descends from neither
aristocrat nor sorcerer,
but is born of an ordinary family.
Ordinary?!
Wait, that's him?
First one since the school
was founded, I heard.
Pretty bold for an ordinary.
Did he get in on connections?
I-I can't believe an
ordinary just touched me...
Wanda!
Wanda! Keep it together!
It's okay! Everything's okay!
Wanda!
So you're Ray White?
And you are?
Albert Alium.
I'm Ray White. May I call you "Mr. Alium"?
Only nobles are allowed
to attend this school,
or, at the very least,
those descended from sorcerers.
That's because the Arnold Academy of Sorcery
has ancient and honorable
origins as a school for nobles!
Yeah, that's right! Totally right!
I don't know what strings
you pulled to get here,
but this is no place for
an ordinary like you!
You tell 'im!
That's unfortunate. There are many
things I want to learn at this academy.
Why, you—
You worthless ordinary!
Enough!
Tch.
Whoa! She's...
From one of the top three noble families.
Al, maybe you should stop...
Lady Rose!
She's such a treasure!
Rose?
Hmph!
I will never accept an ordinary like you!
Hey! Wait up, Al!
Are you all right?
Yeah. Thanks.
I'm Amelia Rose.
Miss Rose.
I'm Ray White.
Feel free to call me "Ray."
And you can call me "Amelia," as well.
You're the first ordinary
to attend this academy.
That's a big deal.
Clearly, your talents have been recognized.
I couldn't be more grateful.
So, Ray...
What is it?
If you have any problems
at all, you can talk to me.
Now, a word from our principal.
Welcome, students.
The Arnold Academy of Sorcery
is among the finest schools in the world.
All of you who stand here today
have been acknowledged for
your talents as sorcerers.
But do not be prideful.
Hard work is still a must.
Spare no blood, sweat, or tears.
One's skills are a product of their innate
talent, environment, and hard work.
Many sorcerers, despite remarkable
talents and favorable environments,
lose heart and let their
abilities waste away.
Thus, I tell you this:
Put in the effort to become
first-rate sorcerers.
I am Abbie Garnet, the principal
of the Arnold Academy of Sorcery.
Thank you.
Thank you for that speech, Principal.
Next,
a word from the representative
of incoming students.
I am Amelia Rose,
representative of the incoming students.
I am proud to have been accepted
to this prestigious academy.
However, this is not our destination,
but rather our starting point.
I'm sure many difficulties
lie on the road ahead of us.
But now that I am a student of this academy,
I intend to face all of them head-on.
As the principal said a moment ago,
to continually work hard
and master our sorcery
is the mission we have undertaken.
That's him?
Look, it's the guy everyone's talking about.
Really?
Silence.
This is the last student to join the class,
the one I've told you about.
I'm Ray White.
As I'm sure many of you know,
I come from an ordinary family.
I've heard I'm the first ordinary
at this school since it was founded,
but I intend to put forth my best effort
as a sorcerer throughout my time here.
I hope we can work together.
Okay, White. Sorry to just throw you
into this, but you know the situation.
You can introduce yourself to
your classmates individually.
Yes, Instructor.
It's Helena Grady. You can call me Miss Gray.
My apologies, Instructor Gray.
Must you be so rigid?
Okay, fine. Go on and sit down.
Yes, ma'am.
Looking forward to working with you, Ray.
Same here, Amelia.
Why is Lady Rose talking to him?
Wait, why? Why?!
One of the three top families
is interested in him?
Ordinary...
White!
Class is in session, White.
You need to pay attention.
I apologize.
To get back on topic...
We were discussing sorcerer ranks.
Do you know what they are, Rose?
Yes, ma'am.
There are five ranks established
by the Society of Sorcery:
bronze, silver, gold, platinum...
and grand, the rank regarded as sacred.
Correct.
Only seven grand sorcerers
exist at any one time.
These seven, who have mastered
the very essence of sorcery,
are known as the seven greatest
sorcerers in the world.
They are the pinnacle of sorcery
that all sorcerers strive to match.
The very existence of the seven greatest
sorcerers is shrouded in mystery,
but a few details about them
are known to the public.
First, our very own principal, Abbie Garnet,
is the Blaze Sorcerer.
Next, the Spellbinding
Sorcerer, Carol Caroline.
She's the most well-known of the
seven as a researcher of sorcery.
In fact, she's just about the only one
who really puts herself out there.
And then there's the one known as
the hero of the Far East War...
The Iceblade Sorcerer.
Exactly.
The Iceblade Sorcerer is the one who vanished
after bringing an end to the Far East War.
Nothing is known about the rest of the seven.
Not even their aliases.
But as I said earlier,
so long as you attend this academy,
you should be aware that the destination
at the end of your path is the rank of
grand sorcerer, one of the great seven.
Miss Gray.
What is it, Alium?
If the goal we strive for is to be
one of the seven great sorcerers,
then why is there an ordinary at this school?
That's right.
Why is there an ordinary?
It doesn't make sense.
The only students here are those
who passed the mandated exam,
as well as an in-person interview
to be approved as students.
Whether they are noble or
ordinary means nothing.
Tch.
Now, it's time to practice some sorcery.
You might not think it necessary anymore,
but you will be starting from
the most basic of exercises.
Do not underestimate the basics.
Even the seven great
sorcerers are no exception.
Now, Rose...
Yes, ma'am.
What is "sorcery"?
Sorcery refers to the art of
reconstructing prima materia,
the primary building block
of matter in our world.
Very good. That's right.
And at the very core of
sorcery is the code theory.
Prima materia, encoding, material code.
First, you encode prima materia,
or in other words, turn it into code.
At this stage, there is still excess data.
So...
Material code, decoding, material code.
You remove the excess by decoding,
put the data back in order,
and move to the processing stage.
Material code, processing.
Here, you can add or remove more data.
Finally, you manifest it.
Embodiment, material.
These are the fundamentals of sorcery.
Additionally, anything you have made...
you can also erase.
Sorcery is a theoretical phenomenon derived
from the understanding of technique.
Any questions about what
I've explained thus far?
I have one, ma'am.
You do, Rose? Very well.
Are there any limits on the things
reconstructed by prima materia?
No, strictly speaking, there are no limits.
It all depends on the
sorcerer's own capability.
Sorcery is, primarily, the art
of creating matter or phenomena.
Matter can be separated into four categories.
Solids.
Liquids.
Gases.
And finally, plasma.
Anything else is classified as a phenomenon.
Anyone else?
U-Um...
When you erased the ice roses earlier,
did you use anti-material code?
No. There is no sorcerer who
uses anti-material code.
Ainsworth's twofold code theory
is doctorate-level material.
Students don't need to understand it yet.
Now for some exercises.
Prima materia, encoding.
Material code.
Material code, decoding.
Material code, processing.
Embodiment, material.
I knew you could do it,
Lady Rose! Magnificent!
Th-Thanks...
Leave it to a lady of one
of the highest noble families.
I love it so, so, so, so, so, so much!
Uh, yeah...
On the other hand...
Hmm... I see.
What was that supposed to be?
That was a child's sorcery.
But didn't the teacher
say he passed the exam?
What's his deal, anyway?
He's totally useless.
Ordinary...
Whoa... Al?!
As a member of the Alium household,
I refuse to acknowledge the existence
of a talentless Withered Wizard!
This is definitely a
historical school building.
Its construction is flawless.
Looking for Ainsworth?
Huh?! Ah...
You asked about it in class earlier.
Oh... Um, I...
Sorry for asking out of nowhere.
I'm Ray White.
Oh... um...
I'm Elisa Griffith.
Nice to meet you, Miss Griffith.
You can call me "Ray."
Oh... And you can call me "Elisa."
Once more, nice to meet you, Elisa.
Same to you.
Dr. Ainsworth is my role model.
So that's why you asked about
the twofold code theory.
Yeah. I want to be just like her.
That's amazing. She's a top-ranking
researcher of sorcery.
Well, it's just a dream.
Do you like Dr. Ainsworth, too?
Yeah. I love her from the bottom of my heart.
Really?! Wow! I've never met
any other Ainsers my age!
Ainsers?
Oh...
That means... fans of Dr. Ainsworth.
Never heard that before.
There's actually a word for them, huh?
I'm sorry for getting so carried away.
I don't mind. Why, though?
Why what?
You have such beautiful hair.
Huh?!
Elisa...
is there some reason?
Well... don't you think my ears are weird?
They're not weird.
They're lovely.
So you're an elf... no, a half-elf, right?
My mother is an elf.
I've been made fun of all my
life because of these ears.
I think you're beautiful, Elisa.
Huh?!
So what need is there to hide them?
I-I'm glad you think so, I guess.
You seem very mature, Ray.
Do I?
Yeah. You don't look like you're my age.
Jeez, kid, you act way too old for your age.
You're too mature!
I guess I do get that a lot.
I thought so.
Thank you for talking to me today, Ray.
Same to you. I look forward to
spending more time together.
Um... See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
Pardon me.
I've been waiting for you, Ray White.
You're Evi Armstrong?
Call me "Evi," Ray.
Oh? I appreciate the invitation.
I'm not like those noble kids.
I don't care if you're an ordinary.
There's only one thing I believe in.
I knew it! Just like I thought!
Evi, you're...
You've got some nice bulk.
Same to you.
You're welcome here, Ray!
Thanks! Nice to meet you!
Huh?
Sorry about that.
I wasn't expecting anyone to be here.
It's all right.
Running so early in the
morning is very impressive.
Are you an incoming student?
Yes. My name is Ray White.
Oh! You're Ray White?
You know of me?
The academy's first ordinary.
You're very famous.
I'm honored.
My name is Rebecca Bradley. I'm a third-year.
Feel free to call me "Rebecca."
I'll do that, Rebecca.
Good, Ray.
Bradley? That's one of the
top three noble families!
Top three noble families?
You really don't know?
Well, I grew up in the countryside.
I don't know much about the nobility.
Rose, Bradley, and Olgren.
Those three families are as
powerful as the royal family,
with just as much influence over politics,
the economy, and everything
else in this country.
That's who the top three noble families are.
So Amelia is...
The eldest daughter of the Rose family,
the highest of the three.
She's got spotless integrity, high morals,
and first-rate sorcerer skills.
She's a genuine, born-and-bred lady.
Evi, you can go on ahead.
Huh?
The instructor wanted to see me.
Okay. Remember, first period
is practical swordsmanship.
We'll have to change, so get there early.
Right.
Whoa!
Are you all right?
Hey! Watch where you're going!
My apologies. I was just
walking like normal, though...
Well, I was running because
I was kind of in a hurry!
So you should have moved aside!
Uh-huh... That's awfully
unreasonable, but I do apologize.
You're weird. Wait...
Aren't you that ordinary?!
I'm Ray White. Nice to meet you,
my charming, pigtailed lady.
Well, you certainly know just where to look!
You actually recognized the
greatness of these pigtails!
Really?
I am the first and the last,
the girl of transcendent, raging cuteness...
The girl who loves and
is loved by pigtails...
I am Claris Cleve...
land!
Wow, how nice.
I'm not familiar with
the "Cleve Land" family,
but I hope we can get along.
What?! You don't know the Clevelands?
I'm sorry. I grew up in the countryside,
so I don't know much about the nobility.
I see. Well, that's fine... yeah.
It's a pretty well-known family, though...
I see... You don't know us, huh?
But I'm sure it's a beautiful family.
That's clear just from looking at you.
You can tell?!
Oh, very well, then!
I'll grant you special permission
to call me "Claris," Ray!
I appreciate that.
I hope we'll get along, Claris.
I suppose I'll let you get along with me!
Anyway, weren't you in a hurry?
Oh, crap!
Well, bye! See you later!
Okay.
Welcome, Ray.
It's good to see you again, Colonel.
None of that, now. You and I have
both retired from the service.
What shall I call you, then?
Just "Abbie."
Am înțeles, Abbie.
Nu te-ai schimbat deloc.
That part of you is so much like him.
It brings back memories, doesn't it, Abbie?
Uh, hey...
Albert Alium and Ray White.
This is no more than a mock battle.
If it looks like it's getting
dangerous, I'll stop you.
Look, it's the Withered.
Hah, the Withered!
Who the heck said he was good, anyway?
Withered?
They call him the "Withered Wizard."
Huh?
I'm Ray's bosom buddy, Evi.
Oh, well, hello... But what does that mean?
It's wordplay.
"Withered" and "Wizard"...
They're practically the same word.
Oh, I get it.
Ray...
Okay, are you both ready?
Someone who can't even use sorcery...
Begin!
...has no right to stand
on the same level as me!
No way!
Not bad, man!
Impossible!
Ray!
That doesn't have too much influence on me.
You... You...
You damned Withered!
No way...
For real?
I'm glad to see you enjoying
your student life,
Ray White...
the Iceblade Sorcerer.
Students! This is the preview for
The Iceblade Sorcerer Shall Rule the World!
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Data viitoare
Having quietly made up his mind,
Ray heads to the place that's a sanctuary
for fierce, impassioned muscle men,
and a garden for pure, elegant young ladies.
"The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest
Sorcerer Begins His Practical Exercises."
Episodul 2
Băiatul care a devenit cel mai puternic vrăjitor
din lume își începe orele practice
Abbie Garnet, signing off!